<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Truc Tran</title><link>http://tructran.me/</link><description>Recent content on Truc Tran</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://tructran.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Carbon Neutrality Software</title><link>http://tructran.me/post/carbon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tructran.me/post/carbon/</guid><description>Design of an Optimized Carbon Neutrality Software for Retrofitted Commercial Buildings For this project, my team and I developed a tool to produce optimal, zero-net carbon retrofits options for commercial buildings in Boston. The tool was created with accessibility and simplicity in mind. The user interfaces clearly labeled inputs from a graphical user interface (GUI). Once the simulation is run, the backend process produces a HTML report that details the building&amp;rsquo;s energy consumption and carbon emissions and evaluates all possible retrofit combinations by weighing energy consumption and cost.</description></item><item><title>Electrochemical Card Failure</title><link>http://tructran.me/post/sensor-card/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tructran.me/post/sensor-card/</guid><description>Predicting the Failure of an Electrochemical Card A consumable cartridge used in a blood gas testing system occasionally fails early. A proportion of these failures are due to the oxygen sensor. For the capstone project, my team and I aimed to predict the early failure of an electrochemical card. We used logistic regression and CART (Classification And Regression Tree) to identify important features. These features were then cross validated within a Random Forest model.</description></item><item><title>Site Deployment</title><link>http://tructran.me/post/this-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tructran.me/post/this-site/</guid><description>Deploying a Hugo Site to Github Pages Using Github Actions I developed this website using the Hugo framework and pushed to a private repository. I created a Github action to build the site and push it to a public repository after each push to the private repo.
Tech Markdown git CI/CD https://github.com/ttran06/ttran06.github.io</description></item></channel></rss>